TAMATI HARVEY-BREWSTER



TAMATIJAMES9@GMAIL. .COM



0413752533

PORTOFILO SITE HTTPS://WWW.TAMATI-HARVEY.ME

MY OBJECTIVE

Is to gain a full-time job in Front end web development

LANGUAGES, LIBRARY'S AND FRAMEWORKS

- Html
- CSS
- JAVASCRIPT
- REACT.JS
- NEXT.JS
- STYLED-COMPONENTS
- SASS
- TAILWIND
- NODE.JS
- MongoDB

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

ORO BIANCO

28/12/2019-01/02/2020

Position: Head chef

From ordering and stock take to service and functions
My staff and I did an amazing job opening this
restaurant and gaining success with the business. Job
includes ordering, daily service, Food Preparation and
maintaining a clean kitchen.

ONE PEAR TREE

15/12/2020-current Position: Chef De Partie

I run my section comfortably and delegate staff members in a calm and positive manner. Currently working here on a casual basis.

QUALIFICATIONS

Certificate 2 Commercial Cookery H.E.A.T - 2010
Certificate 3 Commercial Cookery Chisolm – 2012
Certificate 4 In Information and Technology
(Web-Development) Holmesglen – 2021
Diploma of Information and Technology
(Back end and Front-end development)
2021-Current

ABOUT ME

I am currently studying my diploma in full-stack and I am seeking a full time junior front-end position. Most of my skills are displayed in my portfolio using REACT as my Front-end library with CSS and Styled Components.

I have one semester left in my diploma and I am ready to take my learning to the next level with a job in

Web-development. I am a loyal, hard worker and committed to whatever project I take on. My background is in hospitality for the past ten years, from kitchen hand to head chef my responsibilities as a team player and problem solver has been instilled into my work ethic.